(忆往昔)
是萨姆  鲍比  他有点儿不一样了
It's Sam, Bobby. He's just -- he's different.
让我觉得有点儿不对劲
Something's not right to me.
我  只是无法抛下你和本
I-I can't just lose you and ben.
我和本会呆在这儿  只要可以你随时都能来
Me and ben will be here, and you come when you can.
但要完好无损地回来
Just come in one piece.
你真觉得这样行得通吗
And you really think we could pull something like that off?
值得一试啊
It's worth a shot.
告诉我你究竟怎么了
Just tell me what the hell is going on.
-迪恩  -本  别过来
- Dean? - Ben, just stay there.
-我听到你说...  -我叫你别过来
- I thought I heard you...  - I said stay back!
解药是坎贝尔家的古秘方
Cure's an old Campbell recipe.
至少
At least, uh...
我还有你
you got my back.
不管发生什么  我都能指望你
No matter what happens, I can always count on you,
-对吗  小萨姆  -当然  迪恩
- right, Sammy? - Of course, Dean.
(如今)
他说他会打来  可那些话都是敷衍我
He said he'd call, but of course he never did.
不过  我不明白
But -- I don't know.
就是  我们俩处得挺好的
I just -- we had such a good time.
我是不是该打给他呢  你觉得呢
I-I should call him, right? Do you think?
我该打给他吗  我真不知道
I mean, should I call him? I don't know.
奥利维亚  稍等我一下
Oh. Uh, Olivia, just hold on a sec.
我只想知道真相  仅此而已
I just need the truth. That's all.
我真得挂了  好吗  稍候打给你
I really gotta go, 'kay? Call you later.
-我同情你  -你说什么
- I pity you. - I'm sorry?
你可悲又可怜  所以我同情你
You're sad and pathetic, and I pity you --
所以我才要给你提个醒
Only reason I'm giving you a head's up.
别碰蛤蛎浓汤
Stay away from the clam chowder.
里面可是放了我自己特有的  调味料
I flavored it with my own... seasoning.
嘿  珍
Hey, Jane.
你知道新来的姑娘美斯狄吗
You know that new girl, Misty?
比你辣多了
Way hotter than you.
你说什么
Excuse me?
基本上  她就是个尤物  而你就是个
Basically, she's an eight, and you're a...
三流水平
a three.
还有什么需要吗  夫人
Can I get you anything else, ma'am?
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
我有次开车撞倒了一个流浪汉
I ran over a homeless man once,
我都没停下来看看他是否还活着
and I never even stopped to see if he was alive.
我讨厌妈妈
I hate mommy.
我想在她睡着时烧死她
I want to burn her in her sleep.
我不知道为什么  但你真让我不舒服
I don't know what it is, but you just give me the creeps.
就像不舒服到想呕吐一样
Like I get physically nauseous.
你真可悲
You're pathetic.
失败者
Loser.
绝望  愚蠢
Desperate. Stupid.
孬种
Mousy.
你就是个绝望又可悲的窝囊废
You're a desperate, pathetic loser.
嘿  你能来接我吗
Hey, can you come get me?
你听起来糟透了  喝酒了吗你
You sound awful. Have you been drinking?
我觉得自己快疯了
I think I'm going crazy.
简直要崩溃了
I'm freaking out.
你说的没错  因为你就是个怪胎
Of course you are, 'cause you are a freak.
你就是个疯子
You're certifiable.
每次电话一响  我的胃就会抽搐
Every time the phone rings, my stomach drops.
珍又有麻烦了
Jane with another crisis.
你俨然就是个活灾星
You're a walking disaster.
全家人都在等着你的下一次大崩溃  珍
The whole family's just waiting for your next big breakdown, Jane.
我们简直没有一刻自由的
We're like hostages.
你干嘛不干脆自杀得了呢
Why don't you just go ahead and kill yourself already?
(铁板烧烤&酒吧  大格尔森的快乐之地)
我知道自己看到了什么  鲍比
I know what I saw, Bobby.
我们试过他了
We tested him.
盐  银器等等  所有都试过了
Salt, silver -- everything.
他任那个吸血鬼对我为所欲为
He threw me to that vamp.
我告诉你  那绝对不是我老弟
I'm telling you, it's not my brother.
那么  他就是我们之前从没遇到过的东西
Well, then he's something we ain't ever seen before.
没错  或者就是他妈的路西法
Yeah, or it's freakin' Lucifer.
你召唤小卡了吗
Did you call Cass?
当然召唤了  但没任何回音
'course I called Cass. He's not answering.
去他的  我等不及了
Screw him. I can't wait anymore.
听着  我明白  你有点惊慌失措
Look, I get it. You're rattled.
这很正常
You're right to be.
但我们得专业点儿
But let's be professional --
专业点儿
Professional?
他眼睁睁地看着我被转化
He watched me get turned!
你看到的
What you saw...
你肯定那是你亲眼所见吗
are you sure that's what you saw?
该死的  鲍比  我知道自己看见了啥
Damn it, Bobby, yes. I know.
"你知道"可不等同于证据
Well, "You know" ain't the same as proof.
因为我们谈论的是
'cause we're talking about --
我们是在讨论如何处理这件事  而且要快
We're talking about doing something about this, and fast.
不仅仅是吸血鬼这件事儿
It's not just the vamp.
在他跳下去的那一刻他就变了
He has been different from the jump.
好吧  我支持你
All right. I'm with you.
-真的吗  -是的
- Are you? - Yeah.
我去查资料  认认真真地查
I'll hit the books, hard.
先别一枪嘣了他呢  行吗
Just don't shoot him yet, all right?
好好看着他  我们需要了解实际情况
Watch him. We need facts.
因为如果那不是萨姆
'cause if it ain't Sam...
那我们完全不知道那是什么
we don't know what it is.
而且要想拿下他  我们也得知道方法才行
And if we're gonna put him down, we need to know how.
我甚至都不愿意跟他同车
I don't even want to ride in the same car with him,
更别说跟他一起解决案子了
much less work a damn case.
给我乖乖上车  他就是你的"案子"
Get in the car. He's your case.
嘿  我刚刚  在给莉莎留言
Hey. I was just, uh, I was leaving Lisa a message.
-她还没回你电话吗  -没有
- Still hasn't called you back, huh? - No.
-真糟  -是啊
- Sucks. - Yeah.
你没事吧
You okay?
当然  我很好  你呢
Yeah. I'm fine. How are you?
我  好得很
Me? Great.
这个  你瞧瞧
Here, look. Check this out.
我觉得事有蹊跷
Think it might be something.
四个人  全都是在过去几周莫名自杀的
Four people, out of nowhere, all in the last couple of weeks.
你觉得呢
What do you say?
没错  听起来确实有问题
Yeah. Sounds like a plan.
那出发吧
Let's go.
我搞不明白
I don't understand.
为什么联邦调查局会对自杀案有兴趣
Why would federal investigators be interested in a suicide?
这是一个全新的  更爱民的管理机制
It's a new, more caring administration.
好吧  我已经跟警察都说过了
Well, I already told the cops.
珍那天确实过得挺遭的  我也尽了姐姐职责
Jane was having a really bad day, so I-I did what any sister would do.
我  试着鼓励她振作起来
I...tried to cheer her up, you know?
告诉她坚持下去
Told her to hang in there.
你知道什么叫"说谎迹象"吗
You know what a "tell" is?
什么
Excuse me?
是打牌术语  能说明人们何时在虚张声势
It's a poker term... for when you're bluffing.
就像你刚刚拨头发那一下
Like what you just did with your hair.
你到底想说什么
What are you trying to say?
你在撒谎
You're lying.
什么
What?!
老实交代你对你妹妹做了什么
Tell us what you did to your sister.
好吧  你说得没错
Okay. You're right.
我撒了谎
I was lying.
我本来想告诉她  "我爱你"
I wanted to tell her, "I love you.
"我就在你身边"
I'm here for you."
但是说出来的却是
Oh, but what came out was...
"你这个累赘  你干脆自杀吧"
"You're a burden. Just kill yourself."
谁会说这么残忍的话啊
Who says that?!
但我就是停不下来
I-I-I just couldn't stop!
房子里有什么发现
See anything in the house?
没有巫术袋和硫磺  也没有电磁反应  你呢
No hex bags, no sulfur, no emf. You?
一个大号  还有今天的《编织》杂志
A tuba and an issue of Crochet today.
这算哪门子有自杀倾向
So, what, already kinda suicidal?
对  但是姐姐残忍的吐槽
Right, and then big sis's taxicab confession
把她逼上了绝路
sends her over the edge.
问题是  到底是什么让姐姐
Question is, what made big sis
如此无情地开口喷人
open her big, fat mouth in the first place?
对  这确实是个问题
Yeah, that is the question.
谢谢  能拿点纱布给我吗
Thanks. Uh, can you grab some gauze, please?
真该让你给我开点安定
Should've had you prescribe me a valium.
放松就好
Just relax.
没事的
It'll be fine.
老实说  保罗
I got to be honest, Paul --
我真不想来这里
I don't really want to be here.
没人愿意来这里  但是
You and most people. But you know what?
我不会放在心上的
I don't take it personally.
好的  张开嘴
Okay, open up.
你和堂娜有空应该来吃顿晚饭
You and Donna should come over for supper.
你们都多久没来了
How long has it been?
好了  最难受的步骤完了
There. Worst part's over.
我其实不喜欢堂娜了
I'm not really into Donna anymore.
她老了
She's old.
你妻子风韵犹存呢
Your wife looks great for her age.
她松弛的皮肤让我想吐
Her saggy skin makes me want to hurl.
你知道  我有欲望的
I have urges, you know.
懂
Okay.
还记得那次露营我没去吗  我说我生病了
Remember that camping trip I missed 'cause I was sick?
其实我撒谎了
Well, I wasn't.
我只是害怕和梅利莎在一起
I was just afraid to be around Melissa.
我女儿梅利莎
My daughter Melissa?
但是后来
But then...
她晚上参加了吉尔的睡衣晚会
She spent the night for Jill's slumber party.
一切似乎轻而易举
It just seemed so easy, you know?
你说什么呢
What are you saying?
并不是我无法控制自己
It's not so much I couldn't control myself.
而是我知道不会被人发现的
I just knew I wouldn't get caught.
确实也没人发现
And I didn't get caught.
有什么发现吗
Hey, do you find anything.
我一整晚都在查资料
I've been up all night lookin'.
毫无结果
Nothing fits.
佩服
Awesome.
你还能提供点别的线索不
You got anything else to go on?
和他共处一室  让我毛骨悚然
Yeah, my skin crawls being in the same room with him.
你可以查查这个
Why don't you look that up?
我在想办法啊
I'm working on it.
鲍比  我不知道我还能坚持多久
I don't know how much longer I can do this, Bobby.
你必须尽快弄清楚他到底是什么
You got to figure out what the hell he is and fast.
我在努力中
I'm trying.
但是  迪恩  情形很不妙啊
But, Dean, there's a worst-case scenario.
什么  撒旦是我的搭档吗  我知道
What, Satan's my co-pilot? Yeah, I know.
对  那是另一个不妙的情况
Well, that'd be the other worst case.
那是什么
Well, then what?
可能就是萨姆自己的问题
Maybe it's just Sam.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
-迪恩  -鲍比  给你一天时间
- Dean. - You got a day, Bobby,
否则我就自己动手了
and then I'm handling this.
(莉莎)
又出现一个
There was another one.
是吗  什么情况
Yeah? What?
牙医钻死了一个人
Dentist drilled a guy to death.
你说的  不是在床上那个"钻"吧
You mean the...non-sexy kind of drilling, right?
我赌五十块  他肯定与此事有关
50 bucks says he's mixed up in all the crazy.
-你这么肯定  -是啊  我们去和他谈谈
- You think? - Yeah. Let's go talk to him.
好啊
Okay. Uh...
你先去吧  我马上就来
Why don't you go ahead? I'll catch up.
我还要做点调查
I'm gonna do a little research.
你确定吗
You sure?
对  得搞清楚我们对付的是什么吧
Yeah. We got to know what we're up against, right?
好  好  好主意
Yeah. Yeah, good idea.
(警局)
多谢
Thanks a lot.
钻子男有啥线索吗
Anything from Marathon Man?
没有
Not exactly.
在我来之前他在牢房里上吊自杀了
He hung himself in his cell before I could get to him.
哎哟喂
Yikes.
但是他肯与此事有牵连
But he was definitely involved.
我刚从他助手那里挖到一点线索
Just got the scoop from his assistant.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
这么说吧  当时他的病人对他坦白的那些事
Let's say the stuff that his patient was confessing to --
换做我  我也会杀了他
I'd have murdered him, too.
所以  牙齿穿洞男和吃枪子小妹
So, root canal and russian roulette --
他们两个好像都被诅咒了
both of 'em, it's like they were cursed, right?
人们被迫要向他们
I mean, people are just compelled
吐槽各种实话
to puke the truth all over 'em?
被丑陋的事实打击  然后就走极端了
Oh, getting hit with the ugly truth, you go postal?
那确实是诅咒
I'd call that a curse.
帮个忙
Do me a favor --
我要去太平间查看尸体
I'm going to the morgue to check out the body.
你去牙医的办公室  看看有何线索
Why don't you take the dentist's office, see what you see?
好啊  没问题
Yeah. No problem.
(变幻化妖)
(哈里号角之家)
珍和康利医生
Jane and Dr. Conley.
我听说了  太可怕了
I heard. Awful.
和我有什么关系
What do I have to do with it?
老实说  你是他们唯一的共同点
Honestly? You're the only thing they have in common.
他们死之前  和你说过什么吗
Did they say anything to you before they, uh...?
抱歉  没有
Sorry. Not really.
好吧
Right.
我只是打听一下
Ah, I was just fishing.
谢谢
Thanks.
对了  我的号如何了
Hey, by the way, how 'bout my horn?
什么
Sorry?
失窃的号啊
Stolen horn?
对  我们还在查呢
Right. Yeah. We're -- we're working on it.
希望如此吧  那可是稀罕物
Well, I hope so. Thing's one-in-a-billion.
为什么说它是稀罕物
What makes it one-in-a-billion again?
它是老古董了
It's a museum piece.
据说  已经有一千年的历史了
And near as anyone can tell, about a thousand years old.
它来自哪里
Where's it from?
无人知晓
No one knows.
什么时候被偷的
When did it get swiped?
大概
About...
两周前
two weeks ago --
就是珍死的那天
same day Jane died.
(加百列真理之号)
卡西迪奥  在吗
Castiel? Hello?
这里可能有重杀伤性的天使武器哦
Possible loose nuke down here, angelic weapon.
这事儿应该你们管吧
Kinda your department.
小卡  听到了么
You hear that, Cass?
迪恩  好啊
Hello, Dean.
你又开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我一直在戒备萨姆
I have been on red alert about Sam,
你却为这个该死的号来了
And you come for some stupid horn?!
你叫我  我就来了
You asked me to be here, and I came.
混蛋  我都召唤你好几天了
I -- I've been asking you to be here for days, you dick!
萨姆的事  我没有出现
I didn't come about Sam
因为我没什么好说的
because I have nothing to offer about Sam.
很好啊  因为我们都知道
Well, that's great, because for all we know,
他只是包了个包装的路西法
He's just gift wrap for Lucifer.
不  他...
No, he's...
他不是路西法
He's not Lucifer.
你怎么知道的
And how do you know that?
如果路西法逃出来了
If Lucifer escaped the cage,
我们会感应到
we'd feel it.
那他到底怎么了
What is wrong with him?
我不知道  迪恩  对不起
I don't know, Dean. I'm sorry.
你怎么了  小卡
What happened to you, Cass?
你原来更像人类  至少有点人情味
You used to be human, or at least like one.
我在交战状态
I'm at war.
有些...
Certain...
有些令人懊悔的事需要我去完成
regrettable things are now required of me.
加百列的真理之号  这东西是真的吗
And Gabriel's horn of truth? That's a real thing?
-你见过了吗  -我想就在这镇子里
- You've seen it? - I think it's in town.
某个东西在强迫人们...
Something's forcing people...
得  不客气
Oh, well, you're welcome!
那不是真理之号
It isn't the horn of truth.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你就消失了两秒钟  你都去哪儿看了
You were gone for like two seconds. Where did you look?
哪儿都看了
Everywhere.
得
Right.
随便吧  很高兴见到你
Well, nice seeing you, anyway.
迪恩
Dean.
干嘛
What?
你弟弟的事
About your brother.
我...
I...
我不知道他到底怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with him,
但我是真的想帮忙
but I do want to help.
我会去打听一下
I'll make inquiries.
好  谢了
Yeah. Thanks.
我其实想看一下
Now, I'd actually like to see
这周发生的所有自杀案的尸体
all the suicides that came in this week,
不光吉格斯医生(变态杀人魔)一个
not just Dr. Giggles.
有什么问题吗
Is that gonna be a problem?
那个  他们  他们已经不在了
Well, they're -- they're already gone.
被转移了吗
As in transferred?
也不算是啦
Yeah, not exactly.
你能告诉我这是怎么回事吗
Would you like to tell me what's going on here,
还是我应该跟你上级谈谈
or should I have a little chat with your supervisor?
他们没了
They're gone.
就是...  消失了吗
As in... Gone gone?
...掠夺性竞争削价
...Predatory prices.
接下来是时事报道
Here's the facts.
获知本地队伍的最新获奖消息
Tune in weekdays for the newest addition
请于工作日锁定本台
to our award-winning local team.
彻底了解你待付余款的起居室
Find out the truth about your layaway living room.
再来一杯吗
Another one?
不  谢了  我在工作
Uh, no, thanks. I'm working.
喂  怎么了
Hey, what's up?
尸体都不见了
All the bodies are gone.
你什么意思  就凭空消失了
What do you mean, they just vanished?
验尸官是这么说的  不过我找到了条线索
That's what the coroner said. But I got a lead.
其中一具失踪的尸体
One of the missing bodies,
比其他人早死了整整一周
she died a whole week before everybody else.
也是自杀吗
Suicide?
报告说是车祸
Reported as a car accident,
不过肯定是自杀
but no reason it couldn't have been.
也就是说她是咱们要找的源头了
So then that would make her our patient zero, right?
我想大概是吧
I'm thinking maybe.
不管这东西是什么咒  都是从她开始的
Whatever got this whole curse thing rolling started with her.
我现在在她家
I'm at her place now,
伯恩汉街和159街交叉转角处
corner of Burnham and 159th.
十分钟后到
Yeah, give me 10.
改注意了  再给我来一杯
You know what? I will have that other one.
不是说你在工作吗
Thought you were working.
就指着它工作了
I am working up to it.
你还好吧
You okay?
不太好
No, not really.
我向当地专家询问  为您讲述真相
I talked to local experts to bring you the truth.
我请
On me.
还想要什么吗
Anything else I can get you?
我想要他妈的真相
I'd just like the freakin' truth.
不过再来一杯就好了
But I'll settle for another one.
我有时会觉得  我怀不上孩子
Sometimes I think I can't get pregnant
是因为上帝知道我的婚姻是个骗局
'cause god knows my marriage is a sham.
我为什么说这个
Why'd I say that?
我是说  我每天都要吸镇痛剂的粉末
I mean, I've been snorting oxy all day.
我怎么会说这个
Why'd I say that?
我想我知道为什么
I'm pretty sure I know.
我得走了
I've got to go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我这种姿势坐着  是想让你看到我的胸
I'm sitting like this so you'll look at my breasts.
我刚隆的  我需要很多人的关注
I just bought them. I need a lot of attention.
你加油哈
Good luck with that.
喂  你有什么想告诉我的吗
Hey, anything you're itchin' to tell me?
没什么
Not really.
抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint.
没事儿
Ah, that's all right.
我就是检验一件事
I'm just testing a theory.
我在这儿边啃书
Well, I'm here hittin' the books
边喝牛奶
while drinking a nice glass of milk
还在看"托瑞和迪恩"
and watching "Tori & Dean."
啥  谁和迪恩
Wh-- wait, w-who and Dean?
托瑞·斯佩林
Tori Spelling.
我是她超级粉丝
I'm a huge fan.
姑娘老有才了
Girl's a real talent.
我想在电话里是管用的了
Oh, I guess it does work over the phone.
你知道还有啥吗
You know what else?
我偶尔会修修脚
I get a pedicure once in a while --
那个越南店真的不错
This nice vietnamese joint.
好了好了  别说了
Okay. Okay, please stop.
那妞儿  阿凤
This one gal, nhung phuong --
就是"丝绒凤凰"的意思
Her name means "Velvet phoenix."
人很袖珍  不过那手法啊
Tiny thing, but the grip on her.
她从我脚趾开始
She starts on my toes,
我感觉我要...
and I feel like I am gonna --
够了  行了吧  我那玻璃心都终身创伤了
Whoa, whoa! Hey, come on, m-- now I'm scarred for life.
拜你所赐啊
Thank you.
我从没告诉过别人
I never told anyone that.
为什么要告诉你
Why am I telling you?
可能我比较偏爱你吧
Maybe 'cause you're my favorite.
即使萨姆当猎手更强
Although, Sam's a better hunter.
虽然是最近变强的吧
Lately, anyway.
哇哦  我他妈干嘛要告诉你这些
Whoa. Why the hell am I tellin' you this?!
因为我被诅咒了
Because I'm cursed.
-诅咒  -是的
- Cursed? - Yes.
我就不明白了...
How is it...
有一半时间  你明明是去解决问题的
that half the time you clean a mess,
结果却惹一身腥
you end up dirty?
其实  这可能是这阵子
Actually, this might be the
我碰到的最好的事儿了
best thing that's happened to me in a while.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
迪恩
Dean...
迪恩  你要干什么傻事...
Dean, what damn fool move are you about to --
我要挂了
I gotta go.
好吧
Okay.
你知道吗  我初恋女友其实是...
But did you know my first girlfriend turned out to be a --
够了
No, no.
我是萨姆  有事留言
It's Sam. Leave me a message.
萨姆  是我
Sam, it's me.
听着  我正在去找你的路上
Listen, I'm on my way to you,
如果我到之前你听到了留言  打回给我
but if you get this before then, give me a call back.
有点事要问你
There's a few things I want to ask you.
一场车祸而已
So, why is there an investigation
有什么好查的
for a car accident?
这不是意外
It wasn't an accident.
科莉是自杀的
Corey committed suicide.
你知道
You know...
我曾怀疑过
I wondered.
失礼了
I-I'm sorry.
我只是
I just...
你知道科莉为什么自杀吗
So, you had some idea Corey might have taken her own life?
她最近在学校
Well... She had been going through a bit of a hard time lately...
不太好过
at school.
然后  她的小猫咪咪还跑丢了
And then, um, her cat, Mittens, had just ran away.
但我觉得
But, really
真正的原因是她男友
it was her boyfriend.
她确定他在外边偷腥
She was sure that he was cheating on her.
但他精于善后
But he was just very good at covering his tracks.
这就让她  执著于
Which, of course, made her completely obsessed with --
找出真相
Finding out the truth.
没错
Yeah.
我能看下她的房间吗
You mind if I check out her room?
是我
Hey.
我看到你打过电话来
So.... I saw you called.
对  那次的事太疯狂了
Yeah, it's been crazy.
本连提都不愿提起那事
Ben won't even talk about it.
莉莎  我很抱歉
Lisa, I'm sorry,
但现在
But this is actually the...
实在不是交流的好时机
worst time in the universe to talk.
我们晚点再说好吗
C-can we do this later?
你推了我的孩子  迪恩
You shoved my kid, Dean.
还是现在就把事情说清楚吧
How about we do this now?
事情不是你想的那样
It wasn't like that.
那是怎样
Then how was it?
我无从解释
I can't really explain.
你要听实话是吗
You want to know the truth?
也许不是
Probably not.
你心里有太多秘密
You've got so much buried in there,
你努力把它们埋藏在心底
and you push it down, and you push it down.
你真觉得
Do you honestly think
你能这样安心生活下去吗
that you can go through life like that and not freak out?
靠半夜喝个几百毫升的酒
Just, what, drink half a fifth a night
你就能忘记过去了吗
and you're good?
你知道你嫁的是个什么样的人
You knew what you signed up for.
没错  但我没想到萨姆会回来
Yeah. But I didn't expect Sam to come back.
虽然我真的高兴他没事
And I'm glad he's okay. I am.
但从他踏进我们家门的时刻起  我就知道
But the minute he walked through that door, I knew.
我们完了
It was over.
你们兄弟俩经历的是我这辈子见过
You two have the most unhealthy, tangled-up, crazy thing
最离奇的事
I've ever seen.
只要他活在你的生命里
And as long as he's in your life,
你就永远得不到幸福
you're never gonna be happy.
我没想说得这么难听的
That came out so much harsher than I meant.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
我不是想阻止你接近萨姆
I'm not saying don't be close to Sam.
我跟我妹妹也很亲密
I'm close to my sister.
但要是她死了
But if she got killed,
我是不会把她复活的
I wouldn't bring her back from the dead!
听着  莉莎
Okay, Lis...
我不会骗你
I'm not gonna lie.
我跟萨姆  我们
Okay, me and Sam, we...
我们之间太过纠结
we've got issues.
毋庸质疑
No doubt.
但你和本
But you and Ben --
本和我  不能跟你淌这滩浑水
Me and Ben can't be in this with you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我深表遗憾啊  咪咪
Sorry, Mittens.
你去哪了  我有发现
Hey, where you been? I found something.
这事一会再说  我们得谈谈
It can wait. We got to talk.
好  怎么了
Yeah. What's up?
有些事我一直想问你
There's a few things I want to ask you,
你得实话实说
and, uh, you're gonna tell me the truth.
当然  迪恩  没问题
Uh, yeah, Dean. Of course.
这还用说吗
What are you talking about?
等等  你是说你
Whoa. Are you saying you're...
我想要知道真相
I asked for the truth.
你猜怎么着  愿望成真了
And you know what? I'm getting it.
我已经说了  我有些事要问你
So, like I said, I have a few questions for you.
当那个吸血鬼攻击我的时候
When that vamp attacked me,
你为什么只是站在一旁
why did you just stand there?
我没有
I-I didn't.
我动弹不得
I froze.
你动不了
You froze.
你回来以后就跟个终结者似的
You have been terminator since you got back.
我也不知道  可能是太震惊了
I don't know. Shock?
之后就太迟了
And then it was too late.
对此我非常懊恼
I feel terrible about it.
相信我
Believe me.
迪恩
Dean...
我现在不可能说谎
I can't lie here.
你真的以为
Do you really think
我会故意让那种事发生吗
I would let something like that happen on purpose?
你是我哥哥  你怎么会
You're my brother. H-how could you even --
行了
Okay.
我信你
抱歉
Sorry.
我  以为  我看到些事
I...I thought -- I thought I saw something. I...
大概是我看走眼了
I guess I was wrong.
那天真是一团糟
It's just been a really, really bad day.
没事的
Hey. It's okay.
你还有我  好吗
I got your back, all right?
我一直都在
I always have.
谢谢  小萨姆
Thanks, Sammy.
这就是那小妞曾经的宠物
So this was the chick's pet?
她鬼迷心窍了
Well, she was obsessed.
我想你是说她疯了吧
I think you mean crazy.
好了  猫头骨
All right, so cat skull,
摩洛哥豆蔻种子  荚莲树皮
uh, grains-of-paradise seed, devil's shoestring.
混在一起  就是个召唤术
Mix 'em well, you got yourself a summoning spell.
召唤恶魔吗
Demon?
召唤天神
God.
科莉对她男友的精神背叛
Corey was so desperate for the truth
太渴望得到真相了
about her boyfriend's cheating heart,
她到处打听
she went digging around.
一无所获
Nothing panned out,
于是就换了种方式寻求帮助
so she went looking for a different kind of help.
-也就此打开了一扇难以关闭之门  -是啊
- Opened a door she couldn't close. - Yeah.
现在镇上只要有人要求得知真相
Now anyone in town who asks aloud for the truth
就会召唤出真相女神
invokes Veritas.
当然她不是给完就算
And she doesn't just give it to you.
她会用真相打击你  直到你自我了结
She slams you with it until you kill yourself
成为她的贡品
and she gets her tribute.
那些消失在停尸间的就是"贡品"
So, all that "Tribute" vanishing from the morgue.
你怎么看  像《超世纪谍杀案》的情节吗
What do you think, uh, Soylent-Green situation?
天神也要进食
Gods got to eat, too.
也就是说要么把她干掉  要么你被吃掉
Which means we got to take her out or you're on the menu.
好吧  除了疯狂的猫女
All right, well, what do we know,
我们还知道什么
besides crazy cat lady?
-狗是她的软肋  -合情合理
- Well, dogs are her Achilles heel. - Naturally.
她曾经是位亲力亲为的女神
And she was a pretty hands-on goddess back in the day.
她从天而降
Her thing was coming down from the mountain
向人们吐露真言
to speak truth to the masses.
可她不满足于贡品  她想要受到崇拜
She wanted more than tribute. She wanted to be worshipped.
想受人瞩目的婊子
An attention whore.
你要这么理解也行
If you want to put it that way.
话说  21世纪
And what is the 21st-century version
对大众吐露真言的常用方法是啥
of speaking truth to the masses?
你真觉得这个神化身成了
So you really think this god is slumming
山寨版的戴安·索耶吗(著名ABC新闻记者)
as some farm-league Diane Sawyer?
就当是我的直觉吧
Eh, call it a hunch.
我是艾士莉
I'm Ashley --
我是艾士莉·弗兰克  欢迎收看"吐露真言"节目
I'm Ashley Frank, bringing you "Frank talk."
重来一遍
Let's do that again.
我是艾士莉·弗兰克  欢迎收看"吐露真言"节目
I'm Ashley Frank, bringing you "Frank talk."
重来一遍
Again.
我是艾士莉·弗兰克
I'm Ashley Frank.
有机蔬菜真的货真价实吗
Are organic fruits and veggies really worth the cost?
她真吓人
She's creepy.
光看头发就够吓人的了
I mean, the hair alone.
我也不知道  伙计  也许根本没什么
I don't know, man. Maybe there's nothing here.
我们在录了吗
Are we -- we're spinning?
新的租赁拥有价格...
do the new rent-to-own prices...
家具商店的最新趋势...
...a recent trend in furniture stores...
但在购买大宗物品之前
...But think twice before you decide to buy --
请三思而行
before you make that big purchase...
好吧
Okay.
让我们自己问问议员吧
We'll ask the councilman ourselves.
还在拍吗
Are we still rolling?
等等
Hold on.
快来看这个
Check this out.
放大那里
Zoom in on that.
外表看着挺正常吧
Looks pretty normal, right?
里面肯定见不得人
I'm sure inside it's chock full of creep.
准备好了吗
Ready?
好了
Yeah.
-这是什么  -狗血
- And that's...? - Dog's blood.
我该不该问你从哪儿弄来的
Do I even want to know where you got that?
还是别问了
Probably not.
好吧  我们走
All right, let's do this.
哪里见不得人了
So where's all the creep?
来吃晚餐吗
You came for dinner.
坐好
Mm. Sit tight.
接着就轮到你们了
You're up next.
舌头...
The tongue...
是最美味的部分
Is the tastiest part.
也是谎言诞生的地方
It's where the lies roll off.
我等不及要吃你们的了
I cannot wait to eat yours.
我以前见过不少骗子  但你们两个
I mean, I've seen liars before, but you two?
可真是谎言专家啊
Gold standard.
这就是这职业的光荣之处啊
Point of professional pride.
换作是我  我可不会这么傲慢  迪恩
I wouldn't be so cocky if I were you, Dean.
你也知道充满谎言的生活会是什么下场吧
You know what happens when you base your life on lies, right?
一旦真相大白就...
The truth comes along and...
现在  趁着你们还能说话
so, while you've still got your tongue,
上帝也知道你们心有积怨
God knows you've got an earful.
那就说出来听听吧
I think it's your turn to spill some.
咱们不如来玩玩真心话真心话吧
How 'bout we play a little truth or truth?
我们该先问迪恩些什么呢
What should we ask Dean first, hmm?
一些..
Something...
关于你的事情
Personal about you?
迪恩  我很想知道
Hey, Dean, I'm curious.
你对你弟弟的真实想法
What do you really feel about your brother?
现在好多了
Better now.
昨天我还想趁他睡着时杀了他来着
As of yesterday, I wanted to kill him in his sleep.
之前我觉得他是个怪物
I thought he was a monster.
但现在我觉得...
But now I think...
你觉得什么
Now you think what?
他其实就和我一样
He's just acting like me.
什么意思
What do you mean?
是这份工作
It's the gig.
嗜血无数  最后只能血债血还
You're covered in blood until you're covered in your own blood.
有很多次  你差点就要死了
Half the time, you're about to die.
就像现在这样
Like right now.
我告诉自己想要摆脱
I told myself I wanted out...
想要个家庭
That I wanted a family.
但你在自欺欺人
But you were lying.
不
No.
但我真正擅长的...
But what I'm good at...
是割喉取命
is slicing throats.
我做不好父亲
I ain't a father.
我是个杀手
I'm a killer.
这点无法改变
And there's no changing that.
我现在知道了
I know that now.
所以萨姆回到了你的生活
So, Sam walking back into your life
对你来说肯定是种解脱吧
must have been a relief.
你俩真是天生一对(电影中的情侣连环杀手)
Mallory to your Mickey.
再次重逢的感觉如何
And how do you feel about the band getting back together?
萨姆
Hmm, Sam?
听着
Look
我们所做的事
What we do...
相当艰难
Is hard.
但我们彼此照应
but...We watch out for each other.
这才最为重要
and that's what's important.
就是这样
And that's it.
这是事实
That's the truth.
不
No.
不是
No, it's not.
你自己也说了  我不能说谎
You said yourself -- I can't lie.
你怎么做到的
How are you doing that?
这不可能
That's not possible.
你在撒谎
You're lying to me!
不  我没有
No, I'm not!
你是什么东西  他是什么
What are you? What is he?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
是吗  我强烈怀疑
Really? I doubt that.
你所说的话我一句都不信
I doubt anything that comes out of your mouth right now.
你不是人类
You're not human.
什么
What?
你不知道吗
You didn't know that?
好吧  这我相信
Now, that I believe.
迪恩  是我
Dean, it's me.
你不是我弟弟
You are not my brother.
听我说
Just listen.
你到底是什么东西
What are you?!
是我  迪恩
I'm me, Dean.
听着  求你了  听我解释
Look, please, just let me explain.
见鬼的我干嘛要相信你
Why the hell should I believe anything you say?
好吧  你要知道真相吗  我这就说
Okay, okay. You want the truth? Here it is.
上帝作证  我说实话
Here it is. God's honest.
她说的没错
She was right.
我的确出了问题  很不对劲
There's something wrong with me, really wrong.
已经有一阵子了
I've known it for a while.
我骗了你  没错
I lied to you. Yeah.
我看着你被变成了吸血鬼
And...I let you get turned by that vamp.
因为我知道有解药  迪恩
Because I knew there was a cure, Dean,
而我们必须进入吸血鬼的巢穴
and we needed in that nest!
我知道你能挺过来
and I knew you could handle it!
挺过来
Handle it?!
我可能会死的
I could've died!
也可能会杀死本
I could've killed Ben.
我是不该这么冷酷
And that should stop me cold.
但我没有感觉
But I -- I just don't feel it.
什么
You what?
自从我回来之后
Ever since I came back,
我成了比以前更棒的猎人
I am a-a better hunter than I've ever been!
我无所畏惧
Nothing scares me anymore!
因为我没有了任何感觉
'cause I can't feel it.
我也不知道我怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with me.
我觉得...
I think...
我需要帮助
I need help.